Isn't that too close?
You're just friends
Oh, it's Shindecent
Hyesung
Get up, let's get you home
It's okay
I'll call a cab for him
Cab is fine
but not my car?
Hyesung doesn't want
to see you
Soobin
Thank you
for taking care of him
but I'm his boyfriend
Bullshit
Hyesung
get up
Come with me
I have something to say
I'm sorry
I'm going with Soobin
Damn it!
It's been ages since I
was on the shooting set
Oh, you're here
-Hello, Hyobum
-Hello
You just got here?
No, I talked to
the director for a bit
Oh, you did?
This is my first drama
I'm a little nervous
Right
Oh, and thank you
Hyobum
For what?
I heard
you recommended me
It's all thanks to you
I'm here
No, no
I thought it'd be fun
to work with you
For real?
Yeah